It doesn't have this guy.
He is a dog and only six months old.
His name is Sixten.
He has not thought about going on vacation to Dalarna.
Tonight, on the other hand, he will sleep without me and Amanda for the first time since we picked him up.
For we, we will go to Dalarna in Sweden.
And we will investigate a landscape full of vast forests, mountains and lakes.
We will also live in an incredibly special little cottage in the middle of the woods,
swim in a beautiful lake,
wander up a mountain,
And ride about 65 miles on a motorcycle.
All in less than 30 hours.
So we drive.
But the journey has not even started by the way.
You should see what has happened so far.
We left at 11 in the morning - it was Sunday by the way - and decided to go to Leksand.
To get to Leksand we have to go via Filipstad ...
... and Vansbro.
It's easy to find with the help of signs, but I also cheated and used GPS on the motorcycle.
We stopped and fished at a resting place just before Vansbro…
Now it gets coffee
… And continued to drive north, through Vansbro and towards Leksand.
Amanda tested holding the camera against the asphalt and then we arrived at Leksand.
If you come from the south, you go into Leksand over a powerful bridge.
If you turn right you get down on the quay where there is a restaurant right on the water, and to the left you see Lake Siljan.
Nice it was here
Amazingly beautiful
We ate at the restaurant Marinan and on the menu there were lots of different to choose from.
I took burgers.
Amanda took baked potatoes with shrimp.
And then Gandalf comes ...
Then Gandalf comes like this ...
Now I'm Gandalf then.
Okay.
How about an old friend
And then he gets duck like this.
Yes exactly.
And then he hits the head in the ceiling.
Näsets Marcusgård is thus located in Furudal and is run by a very nice family who received us, showed around, made sure we had a good time and served breakfast in the morning.
A very unique experience simply.
In addition to our cabin, "Oddi's eye", there are, for example, the tree hut "Supermoon" which looks like this.
Then it was evening.
And it was night.
And it was morning.
And it was time to move on.
We would be even deeper into the forest, towards a place called the pea sauce, and the residents of the residents.
Here I started to get used to driving on gravel.
I got better and better confidence and learned how the motorcycle reacts to different types of substrates.
As the fastest, I drove at maybe 60 km/h, with Amanda on the motorcycle and full packing.
Finally we arrived and started wandering up the mountain, towards the residents of the residents.
This sign is not that common.
It's like:
Okay...
... and became unsure whether to go in or not.
Is it just to go in or
No, I don't really think so.
Here they have set up electric fences ...
... which means that you simply must not go in,
But we could just, very easily, go down.
Simsalabim.
Now I have magically come across the other side.
I do not know...
Then we might as well continue
A little more.
Do you also think there may be some kind of bull
Eeh ...
So as in Pettson & amp;
Findus, that you get chased then ...
It would ...
Yes, there is it then we are ...
Then we are unlucky.
But then we have to skip such a fence just.
So really, Amanda, so we have to do it.
Or we must simply drove the bull up.
Just.
Take the bull by the horns.
Hoho
Still, someone has been able to build all these old houses.
Here we will see.
Here we have some kind of sign.
No smoking.
Here's someone.